http://www.simplystamps.com/privacy-policy

15% OFF Address Stamps!
CODE: ADDRESS
CODE: ADDRESS ONLY
Hours
:
Minutes
:
Seconds LEFT ADDRESS
Stamp of the WeekLog OutMy Account Resources Customer ServiceLog In
Simply Stamps
Search
Total: $0.00 Shopping cart items -
$0.00You have no items in your shopping cart.
Address StampsBest SellersChristmasCustom LineDog StampsHanukkahKwanzaRoundShop all ThemesAll Address Stamps Rubber StampsCustom ArtworkCustom Text LineCheckbox StampsPink StampsPre-inkedSelf-inkingWood HandleEco-FriendlyView All Rubber Stamps Logo StampsRectangle LogosRound LogosSquare LogosCatalog StampsLogo & TextPersonalized ArtPre-InkedWood HandleView All Logo Stamps Signature StampsSignature OnlyWith DateWith Printed NameWith LogoView All Signature Stamps Wedding StampsWedding AddressSave the DateWedding InvitationDIY WeddingWedding Thank YouBridal ShowerOther Occasions:Thank You StampsJust MovedBaby AnnouncementStamps for All Occasions EmbossersAddress EmbossersCorporate SealsLibrary EmbossersLogo EmbossersNotary EmbossersShop AllView All Embossers Office StampsBanking & AccountingDate StampsDepositInspection StampsNotary & ProfessionalLoyalty Card StampsNumbering StampsPostage PaidSecurity StampsState SealsTax StampsShop All Teacher StampsGradingFrom the Desk ofMotivationalFeedbackSign & ReturnName MissingFun StampsView All Teacher Stamps CraftingBullet Journal StampsChristmas StampsDecorative StampsDIY Wedding StampsThanksgiving StampsSentiment StampsShop All Ink Stamp Ink and Ink Pads Ink Pad RefillsInk Bottle RefillsEmbosser AccessoriesCraft Stamp Ink
All Shipping Guaranteed Delivery by 12/25Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how SimplyStamps.com (and its affiliates, as defined below) uses and protects any information that you give SimplyStamps.com when you use this website. SimplyStamps.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. SimplyStamps.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.Your Personal InformationWe do not collect personal information when you visit our web site unless you complete a contact form or are an existing customer.Our contact forms request your name (and/or business name), phone number, and e-mail address. This data is collected so that we may respond to your inquiries.We will not disclose your personal information to any person or business who is not an employee or agent of SimplyStamps.com. We may use your personal information to contact you as needed for business purposes, including but not limited to, soliciting feedback about our website, products, and services. We may also contact you to provide customer support, announce new services, or with requests for general information. We honor all requests for removal from any of our e-mail lists.We may share broad demographic or other information about our members with partner companies while withholding your personal identification.We do not share, sell, rent or barter any identifiable personal information to any third party without your permission. How We May Use Your Information:With your consent (where required by applicable law), we may use the information we collect for the following purposes:To send you emails or text messages about the products and services, competitions, offers, promotions or special events we believe may interest you;To send you emails or text messages about the products and services of our business partners;Use cookies and similar technologies;We may use the information we collect about you in other ways, which we will tell you about at the time we collect it and for which we will seek your consent if required by law. Marketing CommunicationsIf you have agreed to receive marketing communications from us, you can later opt out by following the opt-out instructions in the marketing communications we send you or you can also contact us by using the contact details provided under the “How to Contact Us” section above. You can opt out of email, SMS text message marketing, and push notification marketing at any time.If you do opt out of receiving marketing communications from us, we may still send communications to you about your transactions, as well as any accounts you have with us.
Opting out of one form of communication does not mean you’ve opted out of other forms as well.
For example, if you opt out of receiving marketing emails, you may still receive marketing text messages if you’ve opted in to receiving them. Additionally, opting out of one of our websites does not automatically opt you out of all of our websites marketing communications you have previously opted into.Demographic InformationWe may use user information, including Personal Information, behavioral metrics, geo-location data, demographic data and marketing preferences to personalize and display advertisements and other content for you.Newsletters and Product Notification Opt In/OutWe periodically send newsletters and/or new product updates and notifications. Visitors to our website may choose to receive these e-mails. Customers receiving e-mails can opt out in order to prevent receiving future e-mails of this nature. This option is provided at the bottom of every e-mail. We respect your right to decline and have made the process of opting out as easy as possible. Opting out of the newsletters does not remove you from our contact database and you may still receive invoices or emergency website notifications via e-mail.How We Use cookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Limitations of this Privacy PolicySimplyStamps.com takes all reasonable care to protect your information; however, there can be exceptions to this policy whereby we are required to release information about you. Some possible reasons for exception to this policy include but are not limited to, government and court order requests. In the event such a situation arises, you authorize SimplyStamps.com to disclose any content or information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as SimplyStamps.com deems necessary or appropriate.Outside Source Content and MaterialSimplyStamps.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites which we may provide links to.Collection ConsentBy using our website, you consent to SimplyStamps.com collecting and using this information.List of Cookes We May CollectThe table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.COOKIE nameCOOKIE DescriptionCARTThe association with your shopping cart.CATEGORY_INFOStores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.COMPAREThe items that you have in the Compare Products list.CURRENCYYour preferred currencyCUSTOMERAn encrypted version of your customer id with the store.CUSTOMER_AUTHAn indicator if you are currently logged into the store.CUSTOMER_INFOAn encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDSStores the Customer Segment IDEXTERNAL_NO_CACHEA flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.FRONTENDYou sesssion ID on the server.GUEST-VIEWAllows guests to edit their orders.LAST_CATEGORYThe last category you visited.LAST_PRODUCTThe most recent product you have viewed.NEWMESSAGEIndicates whether a new message has been received.NO_CACHEIndicates whether it is allowed to use cache.PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CARTA link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.POLLThe ID of any polls you have recently voted in.POLLNInformation on what polls you have voted on.RECENTLYCOMPAREDThe items that you have recently compared.STFInformation on products you have emailed to friends.STOREThe store view or language you have selected.USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIEIndicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDSThe products that you have recently viewed.WISHLISTAn encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.WISHLIST_CNTThe number of items in your Wishlist. Changes To This PolicyAny future privacy policy changes will be posted on this page to keep you aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Affiliateswww.hcbrands.com, www.customstamps.com, www.nametagwizard.com, www.customsigns.com, www.promo180.com, www.904custom.com, www.corpconnect.com, www.allstatenotarysupplies.com, www.wallmonkeys.com
Company About Us Customer Service Contact Us Blog American MadeMy Account Login / Create Account Forgot Password Manage AccountSupport Shipping Returns Reorders FAQfacebookpinteresttwitterinstagramyou-tubeSave 15% off your order today, Sign up for Email
By signing up, you agree to our Terms and Conditions & Privacy Policy
Save 15% off your order today, Sign up for text & email messages Sign Up Now × Sign Up For Text & Email Messages To Receive Your 15% Off Coupon Now
Phone
E-mail
First name
Last name
By subscribing to this service, I agree to the Terms of Service & Privacy Policy Msg & Data Rates May Apply You have to agree on terms in order to proceed to the subscription.   Thank you for signing up! You'll periodically receive text updates on special deals, new products, and transaction information. Just one more step! We sent a text to   to confirm your subscription. Please reply Y or Yes to finish signing up for messages from Simply Stamps. Simply Stamps: Address StampsCustom StampsLogo StampsSignature StampsInkShop by StateBrands / ModelsStamp TypesVideosAmerican Made ProductsTerms & ConditionsPrivacyContactSitemapRedeem Gift BoxSpecial RequestsTips & Guides © 2020 Simply Stamps. All Rights Reserved.    Guest ID: 48rrf2 Back to Top Login into your Account ×
Login Register
Forgot Your Password?
Forgot Your Password? ×Please enter your email address below. You will receive a link to reset your password.
Submit
Back to Login
Create an account × * All fields below are required.
Submit
Back to Login
